acaiberryacai.com 2009-10-09

# Privacy Policy

We pride ourselves in taking your privacy seriously. We have created below a policy for you to review so that you feel comfortable using our site.

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site.

This site contains links to other sites and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

We sometimes employ infrastructure and technology from other companies to run our website. We agree not to sell or rent email addresses and will only share information as necessary to run our operations.

We utilize a standard technology called ?cookies? and web server log files to collect information about how the website is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs include data such as the date and time of visits and the pages visited.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.
